Guide to the Henrik N. Dullea papers, 1982-1991.
Dullea, Henrik N. papers, 1982-1991.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Henrik N. Dullea papers, 1982-1991.
4-1-2981
Henrik N. Dullea
11.1 cubic ft.
Correspondence, speeches, reports, subject files, and other papers.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, speeches, reports, subject files, and other papers of Dullea, chiefly during his Directorship of State Operations and Policy Management; includes personal correspondence and files relating to Cornell University.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Vice President of Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, speeches, reports, subject files, and other papers of Dullea, chiefly during his Directorship of State Operations and Policy Management; includes personal correspondence and files relating to Cornell University. Also, a set of indexed transcripts from the six public hearings of the Temporary State Commission on Constitutional Revision, 1994, and information on the Lake Course Cooling Project and Graduate Student unionization at Cornell (2002).
SUBJECTS
Names:
Dullea, Henrik N.; Cornell University--Administration.; New York (State). State Operations and Policy Management.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Letters and Memos
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Dec. 1983- July 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Mar. 1984-Dec. 1985 (Box 1, Folder 6-9)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Aug. 1984-Nov. 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10-12)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Nov. 1984-Dec. 1984 (Box 1, Folder 13-15)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Jan. 1985-Feb. 1985 (Box 1, Folder 16-19)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), May-86 (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), June 1986-July 1986 (Box 1, Folder 22-27)
  - Follow up on Various Correspondences, Aug. 4, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 28-29)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Aug. 1986-Sept. 1986 (Box 2, Folder 1-5)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Oct. 1986-Nov. 1986 (Box 2, Folder 6-10)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Dec. 1986 (Box 2, Folder 11-15)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Jan. 1988-Feb. 1988 (Box 2, Folder 16-20)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Mar. 1988 (Box 2, Folder 21-24)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Apr. 1988-June 1988 (Box 2, Folder 25-29)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), July 1988-Aug. 1988 (Box 2, Folder 30-33)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Sept. 1988 (Box 3, Folder 1-4)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Oct. 1988 (Box 3, Folder 5-7)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Nov. 1988 (Box 3, Folder 8-10)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Dec. 1988 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Jan. 1989-Mar. 1989 (Box 3, Folder 12-15)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Apr. 1989 (Box 3, Folder 16-20)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), May 1989-June 1989 (Box 3, Folder 21-25)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), July 1989 (Box 3, Folder 26-28)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Aug. 1989-Sept. 1989 (Box 3, Folder 29-31)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Oct. 1989-Nov. 1989 (Box 4, Folder 1-4)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Dec. 1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Jan. 1990-Apr. 1990 (Box 4, Folder 6-9)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), May 1990-July 1990 (Box 4, Folder 10-13)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Aug. 1990-Sept. 1990 (Box 4, Folder 14-16)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Oct. 1990-Dec. 1990 (Box 4, Folder 17-18)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Jan. 1991 (Box 4, Folder 19-21)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Jan. 1991-Feb. 1991 (Box 4, Folder 22-24)
  - Letters and Memos To and From H. Dullea (in Chronological order), Mar. 1991 (Box 4, Folder 25-28)
  - Gerald C. Crotty - Letters and Memos To and From, Mar. 1991 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: Re: Alfred Lilienthal Visit, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Re: Chair in Jewish Studies and Near Eastern Studies, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Speeches and Speech Materials
  - M. Cuomo Speeches, 1975-1990 (Box 5, Folder 1-4)
  - M. Cuomo Speeches, 1984-1988 (Box 5, Folder 5-8)
  - General Speeches, 1984-1991 (Box 5, Folder 9-10)
  - Speech Materials, 1984-1991 (Box 5, Folder 11-13)
  - Speech Materials, 1980s (Box 5, Folder 14-16)
  - Administrative Analysis, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Swygert Inauguration, Apr. 4, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Pace University, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Downsizing Management Conference, Mar. 1, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - SABA Conference, Feb. 26, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - SAPA- Nelson Rockefeller Award, Sept. 18, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Association of Community College Board of Trustees, Sept. 15, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Public Management Program - Rockefeller Institute, Sept. 14, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - State University College of Optometry Commencement Addr., June 1990 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Cazenovia Commencement Address, May 26, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - The University/ Urban Schools National Task Force, May 10, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - New York State and the State of Education, Apr. 27, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 28-29)
  - Walter Broadnax Farewell Dinner, Apr. 17, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - SUNY Purchase- Salute to the Arts, Mar. 21, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - NYS School Boards Association Legislative Network State Finance and State Aid, Mar. 4, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Sir Cripsin Tickell Event Empire State Museum, Apr. 2, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Art Webb's Farewell, Feb. 6, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Center for Women in Government, Jan. 23, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Capital Cities Luncheon Speech and Comments, Oct. 31, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Syracuse University, Oct. 25, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Goldstein Class Lecture, Oct. 19, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Meeting the Challenges of the 90s, Sept. 11, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Other Papers
  - Education Summit National Group for Education Information, Sept. 1989 (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
  - Work Force Information, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 7-8)
  - Capital Cities- Austin Information, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
  - Texas Employee Information (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Capital City Pamphlets (Box 6, Folder 12-13)
  - Rensselaerville, Aug. 1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Skilled Workers Emeritus, Aug. 28, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Medical Society of the State of New York, Sept. 16, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Meeting/Labor Schenectady Community Service Center, July 6, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Staten Island Forum, June 29, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 18-19)
  - Syracuse - Dissertation Materials (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - H. Dullea - Photos (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Articles about M. Cuomo, 1990-1992 (Box 6, Folder 22-25)
  - Executive Chamber Memos and Letters, 1982-1987 (Box 6, Folder 26-28)
  - Executive Chamber Memos and Letters, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 29-32)
  - Executive Chamber Memos and Letters, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Executive Chamber Memos and Letters, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 34-35)
- SUNY Schools
  - Budgeting the State University of New York (SUNY), July 1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - SUNY Purchase - Information about H. Dullea, President (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - SUNY Purchase, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - "Higher Education in the 80s" -Dullea, Apr. 1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Dullea Executive Chambers Materials, July 1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Opening Remarks: President Dullea, Sept. 2, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - First Impressions and Next Steps -Dullea Speech, Nov. 6, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Dullea college Enrollment Projections VC Freeman Letter, Jan. 1981 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - To College Community: 81-82 Executive Budget, Jan. 1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Letter to Chancellor: re: Budget, Feb. 9, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - To: Purchase College Community 81-82 Budget Round 5, Feb. 1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller Institute SUNY Albany, Aug. 31, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - SUNY Albany- Memos and Articles, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - SUNY Central, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Early 1983 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Mid 1983 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Nov. 1983 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Dec. 1983 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Jan. 1984 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Jan. 1984-Feb. 1984 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Jan. 1984-Apr. 1984 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, May 1984-Sept. 1984 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Oct. 1984-Dec. 1984 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - SUNY- Regents, Engineering Program 1984 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Jan. 1985-Feb. 1985 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Jan. 1985-Mar. 1985 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Apr. 1985-July 1985 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Sept. 1985-Dec. 1985 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Jan. 1986-July 1986 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Aug. 1986-Nov. 1986 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Jan. 1987-Feb. 1987 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - SUNY Budget Report 1988 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, 1985-1990 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - SUNY Purchase Annual Report, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - SUNY New Paltz Arrests, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 35-36)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Oct. 1989-Nov. 1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Fall 1989 (Box 8, Folder 2-3)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Nov. 1989-Dec. 1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Late 1989- early 1991 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - SUNY Purchase Annual Report, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Early 1990 (Box 8, Folder 9-12)
  - Operations Report, Nov. 1990 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - SUNY- Memos, Reports and Correspondences, Late 1990 (Box 8, Folder 14-15)
  - Cornell- Information and Memos, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Cornell- Information and Memos, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Cornell- Information and Memos, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Cornell- Information and Memos, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 19-21)
  - Cornell- Information and Memos, 1987-1990 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Cornell- Information and Memos, 1988-1990 (Box 8, Folder 23-25)
  - Cornell- Information and Memos, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 26-28)
  - City University of New York (CUNY) Crisis, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - CUNY Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1976-1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - CUNY Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - CUNY Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - CUNY Report to Chancellor, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - CUNY Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - CUNY Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 7-10)
  - CUNY Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 11-12)
  - CUNY Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 13-19)
  - CUNY Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1988-1990 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - CUNY Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 21-22)
  - CUNY Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 23-25)
  - CUNY Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 26-29)
- Additional Correspondence and Other Papers
  - Education- Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1983-1987 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Education- Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Education- Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1984-1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Education- Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Education- Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 5-7)
  - Education- Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Education- Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 9-10)
  - Education- Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Education- Information, Memos and Correspondences, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 12-14)
  - These folders all pertain to Mario Cuomo's 1987 trip to the (former) Soviet Union. They contain various information, correspondences and articles from before, during and after the trip. (Box 10, Folder 15-26)
  - These folders all pertain to Mario Cuomo's 1987 trip to the (former) Soviet Union. They contain various information, correspondences and articles from before, during and after the trip. (Box 11, Folder 1-7)
  - H. Dullea's personal correspondences, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 8-10)
  - H. Dullea's personal correspondences, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 11-12)
  - H. Dullea's personal correspondences, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - H. Dullea's personal correspondences, 1983-1986 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - H. Dullea's personal correspondences, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - H. Dullea's personal correspondences, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - H. Dullea's personal correspondences, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - H. Dullea's personal correspondences, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 18-19)
  - H. Dullea's personal correspondences, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - H. Dullea's personal correspondences, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - H. Dullea's personal correspondences, 1988-1991 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - H. Dullea's personal correspondences, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Message to the Legislature - Governor Mario M. Cuomo, Jan. 9, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 1985 State of the State (third draft), Jan. 2, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 1985 State of the State (second draft), Dec. 21, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 1985 State of the State (first draft), Dec. 10, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Public Hearing Transcripts I-II (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Public Hearing Transcripts III-IV, Aug. 29, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Public Hearing Transcripts V, Aug. 29, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Public Hearing Transcripts VI, Aug. 29, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Lee Teng-hui Visit to Cornell, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Lake Source Cooling
  - Lake Source Cooling Subcommittee Briefing Book - 1, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Lake Source Cooling Subcommittee Briefing Book - 2, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Lake Source Cooling, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Re: Lake Source Cooling - 1, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Re: Lake Source Cooling - 2, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Lake Source Cooling General Information, 1999-2001 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Re: Lake Source Cooling, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Graduate School Unionization
  - Cornell Graduate School Unionization - 1, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Graduate School Unionization - 2, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Graduate School Unionization - 3, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Cornell Graduate School Unionization - 4, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Cornell Graduate School Unionization - 5, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Cornell Graduate School Unionization - Correspondence and Web Page Items, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Graduate School Unionization - Correspondence and Web Page Items, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Cornell Graduate School Unionization - Sample Documents from other Grad. Student Union Election Campaigns, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 26)